<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>

    <string name="news_a">
        Civilization 7 PC Specs Revealed: Here are the Requirements for Minimum, Recommended, and Ultra Settings.
        Publisher 2K Games and developer Firaxis Games have published Sid Meier’s Civilization 7 PC requirements ahead of its launch early next year.
        The team behind the latest addition to the historically based 4X series detailed minimum,recommended, and ultra settings for PC users
        in a post on X/Twitter. It’s an extensive list of everything players need to know before they plot a course for their grand global plans,
        letting them know what they’ll need if they want to dive in when launch arrives in February. Although Civilization 7 is also scheduled to come to MacOS
        and Linux/SteamOS, 2K says it doesn’t have requirements to share for these platforms “at this time.”
    </string>

    <string name="news_b">
        Magic: The Gathering Developer Responds to Fears It’s Only Focused on Short-term Profits.
        Magic: The Gathering is currently riding high, consistently breaking its own records as it continues to
        grow into the most popular version of itself in its entire 31-year history. But ask some longtime players
        about its “Universes Beyond” crossovers or the increased pace of new products in recent years and you’ll
        hear a common fear being voiced: developer Wizards of the Coast, pushed by aggressive goals set by
        parent company Hasbro, is only prioritizing short-term gains at the cost of the long-term sustainability of this game.
    </string>

    <string name="news_c">Tales of Graces F Dev Talks About Tales of the Abyss Remaster Possibilities and the Future of the Series.
        Bandai Namco recently announced Tales of Graces f Remastered as the first title in the Tales Remastered
        Project, celebrating the Tales of 30th anniversary. We both got to go hands-on with Tales of Graces f
        Remastered and speak with the game’s producer, Yuki Ishikawa, who talked to us about the series’ future and the possibility of a Tales of Abyss Remake.
        First, we asked why Tales of Graces f Remastered was chosen as the first title in the Tales of Remastered
        Program. One, Graces f is one of the more beloved titles of Tales of, Ishikawa said. It’s especially heralded
        for its battle system. Two, it was just “good timing to make this a remastered title.”
    </string>


    <string name="news_d" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">Joker: Folie à Deuxs Biggest Surprise Is a Repeat of a Controversial Marvel Moment.
        In what is sure to be one of the more divisive releases of the year, Joker: Folie à Deux is now in theaters.
        The sequel to the 2019 smash hit is once again directed by Todd Phillips, who doesn’t seem to be
        enjoying as rapturous a reception this time around. IGN’s Siddhant Adlakha gave the film a 5/10 in his review
        , and many other critics agree with him. The DC sequel has been criticized for its sluggish pace, unfocused tone,
        poorly directed musical sequences, and for criminally underutilizing Lady Gaga, to the point that it makes
        one wonder why they even bothered paying for her to be in the movie. But perhaps worst of all is how Joker 2’s
        twist ending renders both this film and its predecessor kind of pointless.


    </string>

    <string name="news_e">Xbox Made The Right Call Skipping a PS5 Pro Competitor.
        The PS5 Pro, with its jaw-dropping price tag, is now a known quantity after months of rumours and
        speculation. But while I totally get the thinking behind mid-gen upgrades — console cycles are lengthy,
        especially compared to other tech — the PS5 Pro is a really tough sell, even for the most passionate fan.
        That’s why I firmly believe Microsoft has made the right call not to bother with its own PS5 Pro competitor.
        The last time we had mid-gen systems in the PS4 Pro and the Xbox One X, 4K TVs were becoming much
        more commonplace so an upgrade that supported this tech made total sense. Additionally, Microsoft
        also had a weak console launch with 2013s Xbox One and so there was an opportunity to flip the
        narrative by pushing out an upgrade. That’s exactly what happened, because the Xbox One X was a
        fantastic system and arguably the one to go for compared to PS4 Pro, because it provided a bigger leap
        from the base Xbox One and was ultimately more powerful than Sony’s offering. The One X certainly
        made the back half of last-gen a much better place to be as an Xbox fan and a follower of the industry.
    </string>

    <string name="news_f">Halo Infinite Is Officially Getting a Third-Person Mode This November.
        In some major (and pretty surprising) news for Halo fans, Halo: Infinite is finally getting a third-person mode this November.
        343 Industries announced the news on Friday during a Forge panel at the 2024 Halo World Championship.
        For those who arent at the event, the announcement was also posted on X/Twitter, including a bit of work-in-progress footage of third-person mode in action:
        Experience a new way to play!
        3rd Person Mode is coming to Halo Infinite this November ? pic.twitter.com/WkDkGLx8fF— Halo (@Halo) October 4, 2024
        As fans will know, this marks the first time a third-person mode has ever been officially offered in a Halo game.
        Senior community manager John "Unyshek" Junyszek and Skybox Labs senior software engineer Colin Cove offered a bit more information
        at the Halo World Championship panel, saying theyll be starting with third-person Firefight mode in a future update, "but we also have the ability
        to do in PvP and control it in Forge," per Cove.

    </string>

    <string name="news_g">Joy-Con vs. Nintendo Switch Pro Controller: Which Should You Buy?
        The Nintendo Switch is a versatile machine that blends the experience of a handheld and console. While every console comes
        with a pair of Joy-Con controllers, Nintendo also sells a Pro Controller that offers a more traditional gaming experience.
        While both Switch controllers have their own appeal, you may find yourself asking which one is best for you.
        Every Nintendo Switch comes with a pair of Joy-Con controllers attached, which includes both the left and right controller.
        But if you want to pick up some additional Joy-Con for multiplayer games, need a replacement set,
        or just want to mix and match with the dozens of awesome colors, then an additional set of Joy-Con retails for $79.99.
    </string>

    <string name="news_h">Zelda Fans Are Overlaying the Echoes of Wisdom Map With A Link to the Past, and Making Some Surprising Discoveries.
        Now that The Legend of Zelda: Echoes of Wisdom is out, more and more players are fully exploring its top-down, toy-like, open world.
        And theyve gradually been discovering a pretty cool secret about its map: it "links" up almost perfectly with the map from A Link to the Past.
        More and more players have been sharing posts on social media comparing the maps of Echoes of Wisdom and A Link to the Past,
        and have figured out that Echoes of Wisdom basically uses the same map from A Link to the Past… just expanded.
        A number of major landmarks can still be found in the same spots as in Link to the Past, though theyve changed or aged seemingly with the passage of time.
    </string>

    <string name="news_i">Sword Art Online Developer Wants to Take the Series in a More Mature Direction
        New entries of both the Sword Art Online anime and the games have consistently been released for more than ten years now.
        On October 4th, both the newest anime season, Sword Art Online Alternative: Gun Gale Online II, and the newest game,
        Sword Art Online: Fractured Daydream were released.
        SAO: FD is already quite different from the previous in the video game series, but we had to ask: What’s next for the Sword Art Online video games?
        Here’s what SAO: FD producer Shoehei Mogami and SAO game series producer Yosuke Futami had to say about the possibility of a more mature SAO game
        and the MMORPG-style SAO game they know fans want.
    </string>

    <string name="news_j">NHL 25 - Review.
        Every year I get my hopes up thinking, “This is it: This’ll be the year that EA’s NHL finally gets it together and delivers on its full potential,”
        only to then spend dozens of hours playing a game that is almost fundamentally the same as the one I played the previous year.
        There are rare exceptions to this; even though I had my issues with NHL 24, the Sustained Pressure System and Exhaustion Engine at least
        added something new to the overall gameplay, and NHL 21’s Be a Pro Mode has become a staple since its introduction.
        Unfortunately, NHL 25 isn’t one of those exceptions. Despite an overhauled Franchise Mode and updated AI,
        this ultimately just feels like a shinier version of last year’s entry.
    </string>


</resources>